[
  {"question": "Is California a country?","answer": false},
  {"question": "Did 2022 pass yet?","answer": false},
  {"question": "Did Riot Games make League of Legends?","answer": true},
  {"question": "America is a state?","answer": false},
  {"question": "Texas is a state?","answer": true},
  {"question": "Florida is a state?","answer": true},
  {"question": "Japan is part of America?","answer": false},
  {"question": "There are 24 hours in a day?","answer": true},
  {"question": "McDonald's is a clothing store?","answer": false},
  {"question": "Chicken nuggets taste good","answer": true}

]